<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Open Work Mega List</title><link>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/</link><description>Recent content on Open Work Mega List</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Creative Commons BY-SA 4.0. Site theme maintained by UNICEF. Original theme, Dot, created by ThemeFisher.</copyright><atom:link href="https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Continuous Integration (CI)</title><link>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/publishing/continuous-integration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/publishing/continuous-integration/</guid><description>Table of Contents 1. What is CI and why does it matter? 1.1. Tests vs. CI 1.2. Benefits 2. CI platforms 3. Tips and tricks 4. Examples 5. Other resources This guide is an introduction to Continuous Integration (C.I.) for Open Source projects. In this guide, you will learn about the following topics:
1. What is CI and why does it matter? Continuous Integration can be a few different things.</description></item><item><title>Fedora Project</title><link>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/reference-tracking/fedora/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/reference-tracking/fedora/</guid><description>Table of Contents 1. What is Fedora? 1.1. Linux kernel distribution 1.2. Project 1.3. Community 2. Background 3. Get involved with Fedora &amp;#34;Fedora&amp;#34; is not only a kind of hat, but also a large Open Source community with a unique role in the Open Source ecosystem. This page provides an overview of the Fedora Linux distribution, project, and community.
1. What is Fedora?</description></item><item><title>Intro to Creative Commons licenses</title><link>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/forges/creative-commons/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/forges/creative-commons/</guid><description>Table of Contents 1. What are Creative Commons licenses? 2. Acceptable licenses for UNICEF Venture Fund 3. Free Cultural Works 3.1. Why does UNICEF prefer Free Culture licenses? 4. Resources 1. What are Creative Commons licenses? The Creative Commons licenses are a family of licenses meant for &amp;#34;open&amp;#34; content. The licenses are maintained by the Creative Commons, &amp;#34;a nonprofit organization that helps overcome legal obstacles to the sharing of knowledge and creativity to address the world’s pressing challenges.</description></item><item><title>Public Lab</title><link>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/reference-tracking/public-lab/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/reference-tracking/public-lab/</guid><description>Public Lab is a community of practice that has informally collaborated with UNICEF Innovation Fund team members in the past. To learn more about this community, reach out to your assigned Open Source Mentor or see the contact info below.
1. About Public Lab Access to knowledge is a fundamental right. When people want to investigate their environment, Public Lab is the place to go to find and share knowledge, equipment, and community.</description></item></channel></rss>