<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>advocacy on Open Work Mega List</title><link>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/categories/advocacy/</link><description>Recent content in advocacy on Open Work Mega List</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Creative Commons BY-SA 4.0. Site theme maintained by UNICEF. Original theme, Dot, created by ThemeFisher.</copyright><atom:link href="https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/categories/advocacy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Berkeley Initiative for Transparency in the Social Sciences</title><link>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/advocacy/berkley-institute-for-transparency-in-social-science/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/advocacy/berkley-institute-for-transparency-in-social-science/</guid><description>Table of Contents 1. What do they do? 2. Why might this be important to me? 3. Considerations to make The Berkeley Initiative for Transparency in the Social Sciences works to improve the credibility of science by advancing transparency, reproducibility, rigor, and ethics in research.
https://www.bitss.org
1. What do they do? They collaborate with researchers, students, faculty, publishers, and funders across disciplines to:
Generate evidence on problems and solutions in science through meta-research led by BITSS investigators and our broader community.</description></item><item><title>Chorus</title><link>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/advocacy/chorus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/advocacy/chorus/</guid><description>Table of Contents 1. What do they do? 2. Why might this be important to me? 3. Considerations to make CHORUS brings together funders, publishers, institutions, and the public from across the open research ecosystem to share knowledge, develop solutions, advance innovation, and support collective efforts.
https://www.chorusaccess.org/
1. What do they do? CHORUS does a number of things:
Provide trusted information about the outputs of funded research</description></item><item><title>Code of Science and Society</title><link>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/advocacy/code-for-science-and-society/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/advocacy/code-for-science-and-society/</guid><description>Table of Contents 1. What do they do? 2. Why might this be important to me? 3. Considerations to make CS&amp;amp;S is a US-based 501(c)(3) nonprofit supporting open collaboration in public interest technology through fiscal sponsorship and other programs supporting sustainable open source.
https://codeforscience.org/
1. What do they do? They currently have three primary services:
They serve as a fiscal sponsor for a number of projects</description></item><item><title>SHARE</title><link>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/advocacy/share/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/advocacy/share/</guid><description>Table of Contents 1. What do they do? 2. Why might this be important to me? 3. Considerations to make SHARE is a community open-source initiative developing tools and services to connect related, yet distributed, research outputs, enabling new kinds of scholarly discovery. The National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) is currently supporting SHARE in a project to integrate digital humanities into the scholarly web.
https://www.share-research.org/
1.</description></item><item><title>SPARC</title><link>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/advocacy/sparc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/advocacy/sparc/</guid><description>Table of Contents 1. What do they do? 2. Why might this be important to me? 3. Considerations to make SPARC is a non-profit advocacy organization that supports systems for research and education that are open by default and equitable by design. We believe everyone should be able to access and contribute to the knowledge that shapes our world.
https://sparcopen.org/
1. What do they do? SPARC is predominantly an organization which advocates for change through policies and events:</description></item><item><title>Wellcome</title><link>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/advocacy/wellcome/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/advocacy/wellcome/</guid><description>Table of Contents 1. What do they do? 2. Why might this be important to me? 3. Considerations to make Wellcome supports science to solve the urgent health challenges facing everyone.
We support discovery research into life, health and wellbeing, and we’re taking on three worldwide health challenges: mental health, infectious disease and climate.
Wellcome is a politically and financially independent global charitable foundation, funded by a £38.</description></item></channel></rss>