<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Identity Management on Open Work Mega List</title><link>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/identity/</link><description>Recent content in Identity Management on Open Work Mega List</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Creative Commons BY-SA 4.0. Site theme maintained by UNICEF. Original theme, Dot, created by ThemeFisher.</copyright><atom:link href="https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/identity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gravatar</title><link>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/identity/gravitar/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/identity/gravitar/</guid><description>Table of Contents 1. What do they do? 2. Why might this be important to me? 3. Considerations to make Gravatar is a service for having one profile in lots of places.
https://en.gravatar.com/
1. What do they do? Gravatar is a free service that allows for websites to import people’s profiles &amp;amp; profile photos without having to host &amp;amp; maintain them.
2. Why might this be important to me?</description></item><item><title>ORCID</title><link>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/identity/orcid/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nolski.github.io/open-work-megalist/identity/orcid/</guid><description>Table of Contents 1. What do they do? 2. Why might this be important to me? 3. Considerations to make ORCID provides a persistent digital identifier (an ORCID iD) that you own and control, and that distinguishes you from every other researcher. You can connect your iD with your professional information — affiliations, grants, publications, peer review, and more. You can use your iD to share your information with other systems, ensuring you get recognition for all your contributions, saving you time and hassle, and reducing the risk of errors.</description></item></channel></rss>